Is it sensible
Which one is sensible there
Am tarqushay in haqqir
Or that for you to live
To be patient regarding the
prohibition of
ariba
To be patient regarding the
prohibition of
banditry and kidnapping
To be patient regarding not
killing people
in political office
You are patient regarding
that
Let me leave it if it
involves
haram
Let me leave it if it
involves
haram
Is this one
Is this better for you to
leave
something that is haqqir,
despicable
It is even small
It will leave you in a very
short time
This is the enjoyment of this
dunya
That is the comfort,
that is your haqq,
your yatch, your private jet
They are haqqir, sagir,
munkathein and qarib
They are despicable
They are small things,
they are sagir
They are munkathein and qarib
They will become disconnected
from you in
a very short time
Is there anybody who has
enjoyed riding
a yatch
Or a private jet in 70,
80 years
It is munkathein and a very
small
time now they will leave you
Is this one better,
is it better for you to
sacrifice
this one
Why I don't want to eat riba
Why I cannot involve in
kidnapping
banditry
I cannot steal government
money